翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
So the IntList we've built so far can technically do all the list stuff you might want to do,
从技术上讲，我们现阶段构建的 IntList 可以完成你想要的 List 工作
but it's a little awkward to use,
但用起来有点笨拙
as we can see from this syntax.
就像从这个语法中看到的那样
Now, in this case, building a list,
这样的 List
while it's a little awkward, isn't so bad.
有点笨拙，但还不错
We'll find that things like getting the i-th element from the list or asking for the size of this list are going to be quite annoying to do.
我们发现，取 List 的第 i 个元素或计算 List 大小这样的事情很烦人
So to deal with this, what we're going to do
为了解决这个问题
is add a size method and an iterative size method that are going to behave kind of like the length method in Python.
添加一个 size 方法和一个 interativeSize 方法
它们类似于 Python 中的 length 方法
So in Python, we might do something like print len of l,
在 Python 中，我们打印 L 的长度
and we expect it to say three.
预计结果是3
There are three items in the list.
List 中有3个子项
So we're going to do right now is write a method for IntList that takes care of that for us so that we can ask,
所以我们要为 IntList 编写一个方法，可以为我们处理请求并返回
for example, what is the size of our list?
例如 List 有多大？
So we could technically write a loop here or do whatever to get the size the loop,
我们可以在这写一个循环，或者获取循环的大小
but what I want to do instead is write a method to make it easier for the user.
但我想编写一个更便于使用的方法
Because it certainly should be the case that someone should have to loop over a data structure in order to get its size.
毫无疑问，获取数据结构的大小必须循环
It should be easy for the person using the list.
这会方便 List 的使用者
So what I'm going to encourage you to do
所以我鼓励你们
at this point is you should consider writing the size method
考虑编写 size 方法
or thinking about how it's going to be written.
或者思考如何编写
And I'm going to make a note here,
我在这记录一下
which is that this method is going to return the size of the list using recursion.
此方法使用递归返回 List 的大小
So if you are a little rusty on this, this is great practice.
如果你对递归有些生疏，这是个很好的练习
And you can think what should this method maybe look like?
想一想这个方法应该是什么样子的？
So pause the video maybe.
或许可以暂停视频
But I'll go through it now.
不过我现在讲吧
So hopefully, you're pretty familiar with recursion.
希望你们熟悉递归
You're comfortable with it to some degree.
可以轻松使用
And if not, bummer that your prerequisites aren't great,
如果不是，很遗憾你的基础不是很好
but you'll catch up.
但你会赶上的
I don't know what this gesture was that I just did.
我不知道刚才做的这个手势是什么
That was like a sad face gesture,
就像一个悲伤的表情
but didn't really commit to it, I guess.
没认真考虑它
Anyway, so, in a recursive method, what we always need is a base case, correct.
不管怎样，递归中总需要一个边界条件
So what we're going to do is think about what the base case might be.
想一想边界条件可能是什么
So what is the type of list where we know the size?
计算大小后 List 是什么类型的呢？
Well, it's going to be one where we can say that the rest is null.
rest 应该为 null
If the rest is null, that means we have a first value and nothing else, in which case we should return what?
如果 rest 为 null，意味着只剩下一个值，此时应该返回什么？
1.
So if we have a list that only has one thing,
如果 List 中只有一样东西
then the rest will be null, and we'll return 1.
那么 rest 将为 null，返回1
Now, if that's not the case, then what?
其他情况呢？
Well, in that case, we know that it's going to be 1 plus however big the rest of the list is,
不管 rest 指向的 List 多大，都应该加1
and we can get that by just asking for this.rest.size.
只需要获取 this.rest.size() 就可以了
So I'm going to ask my rest-- you know, it's also an IntList-- what size are you?
我问一下我的 rest，它也是一个 IntList，“你有多大？”
And assuming the list is well formed,
假设 List 格式良好
we'll eventually get to this base case,
最终会达到边界条件
and we'll get a nice answer.
得到一个好的答案
Now, it may be the case that you're not super comfortable with recursion,
你可能对递归不太熟悉
in which case I'm going to run this thing through the visualizer.
我要通过 visualizer 来运行这个东西
And if you're already feeling pretty comfortable with this, this might be a little boring.
如果你使用递归游刃有余，接下来会有点无聊
But let's check it out and see how it goes.
不过一起来看看吧
First of all, let's just click last to make sure we get the right answer.
首先点击 Last 确保得到正确的答案
And so indeed we do.
确实如此
We get 3, which means that printed out correct.
我们得到3，这意味着打印的结果正确
So let's run through it step by step.
再来一步一步地来看一遍
After the IntLists are all created,
所有 IntList 被创建之后
we finally get to the point where we're going to ask for the size.
终于到了计算大小的地方了
So we say to l, hey, what size are you?
我们对 L 说：“你有多大？”
So l takes over, and now l is this.
L 接手了问题， 现在 L 指向这个
And thinks, OK, is my rest null?
然后想：“我的 rest 是 null 吗”
No.
“不是”
OK, so what I should do, then,
“好，那么我应该”
is I should ask my buddy right here what its size is,
“问问这里的朋友它有多大”
and I'll add 1 to that.
“我会在此基础上加1”
So I go over here.
所以走到这里
And this is my middle list, and it says, OK, yeah,
这是中间 List，它说：“好的”
now I'm active list.
“现在轮到我了”
So is my rest null?
“我的 rest 是 null 吗”
No.
“不是”
So I'm going to return 1 plus my buddy's size.
“所以我要在朋友的返回值加1”
Finally, we get the last list.
终于到了最后的 List
It's the active list.
这时当前活跃的 List
And that list says, yes.
List 说：“好的”
OK, you know what?
你知道吗？
Rest is null.
“rest 为 null”
I'm a tiny list.
“我是个很小的 List”
I have no successors.
“没有继任者”
There's no rest, so my size is just one.
“没有 rest，所以大小为1”
So I'm going to tell the world.
“我要告诉全世界”
I'm going to shout it from the rooftops, to whoever who was asking, my return value is 1.
“我要在站在屋顶大喊，不管谁问，我的返回值是1”
OK, great. Your return value is 1, so if my sublist is size 1,
“太好了，你的返回值是1，所以我的子 List 大小为1”
then my size must be 2.
“那么我的大小是2”
So I return 2.
“所以我返回2”
Finally, we get back to this list,
最后回到这个 List
and it has reported that it's rest is size 2.
它的 rest 的大小为2
Now, if my rest is size 2 and I'm only one additional value,
“我的 rest 大小为2，我额外还有一个值”
I'm going to add 1 to that, and I will finally return 3.
“加1后返回3”
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
And that's the whole story.
这就是整个故事的来龙去脉